{
    "subject": "resource/Famous_Studios",
    "predicate": "ontology/keyPerson",
    "object": "resource/Howard_Post",
    "human_readable": "A key person at Famous Studios is Howard Post.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9102288484573364,
            "question": "Were there other key people besides Howard Post at Famous Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9098621606826782,
            "question": "Who worked with Howard Post at Famous Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8963251113891602,
            "question": "What was Howard Post's role at Famous Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7925724387168884,
            "question": "Who is Howard Post?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.736188530921936,
            "question": "What impact did Howard Post have on Famous Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5010021328926086,
            "question": "What is Famous Studios known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3629138469696045,
            "question": "Where was Famous Studios located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30490052700042725,
            "question": "What type of company was Famous Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2576977610588074,
            "question": "Can you name any famous works produced by Famous Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17847208678722382,
            "question": "When was Famous Studios founded?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=A key person at Famous Studios is Howard Post.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7297_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any famous works produced by Famous Studios?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7297_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of company was Famous Studios?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7297_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Famous Studios located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7297_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7297_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7297_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7297_154.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7297_167.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7297_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7297_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7297_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7297_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7297_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7297_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Howard Post was the head of Paramount Cartoon Studios and later held a position at Famous Studios, indicating he was indeed a key person there."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}